Stephen J. Gould papers M1437
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Columbia University
  - Geomorphology (Box 538, Folder 7)
  - Geosynclines (Box 538, Folder 8)
  - Growth and form in snails (Box 538, Folder 9)
  - Notebook - History of fishes (Box 538, Folder 10)
  - Notebook - History of fishes II (Box 538, Folder 11)
  - Notebook - History of mammals (Box 538, Folder 12)
  - Notebook - Invertebrate paleontology (Box 538, Folder 13)
  - Invertebrate paleo. (Box 538, Folder 14)
  - Mammals (Box 538, Folder 15)
  - Mayr on taxonomy (Box 539, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box 539, Folder 2)
  - Molecular (Box 539, Folder 3)
  - Notebook - Natural Sciences X (Box 539, Folder 4)
  - Notebooks - Philosophy (Box 539, Folder 5)
  - Philosophy (Box 539, Folder 6)
  - Pleistocene geology (Box-folder 539-7, Box-folder 539-8)
  - Reptiles (Box 539, Folder 9)
  - Short papers - corals fish (Box 539, Folder 10)
  - Snails (Box 539, Folder 11)
  - Notebook - Philosophy (Box 539, Folder 12)
  - Notebook - Stratigraphy (Box 539, Folder 13)
  - Notebook - Stratigraphy II (Box 539, Folder 14)
  - Notebook - Stratigraphy III (Box 540, Folder 1)
  - Strat paleo (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - Stratigraphy of Southeastern Wyoming (Box 540, Folder 3)
  - Submarine geography (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - Notebook - Submarine geography (Box 540, Folder 5)
  - Taxonomy (Box 540, Folder 6)
  - Topographical maps (Box 540, Folder 7)
  - Vertebrate paleo - History (Box 540, Folder 8)
  - V. P. seminar (Box 540, Folder 9)
  - Music programs (Box 540, Folder 10)
  - Music programs (Box 541, Folder 10)
- New York University